(Howard:)I bet whoever invented
tiny umbrellas
(Howard:)doesn't have to worry
about money.
(Howard:)He can have
all the kids he wants.
(Sheldon:)And can keep a small portion
of their heads dry.
(Howard:)If I'm gonna have any chance
of raising this kid,
(Howard:)I need to come up with
a big idea to make some money.
(Leonard:)There's no reason you can't.
That's easy for you to say.
(Howard:)You and Sheldon
already came up with
(Howard:)your superfluid helium model.
(Leonard:)That's just research.
We're never gonna
(Leonard:)make any money from it.
(Sheldon:)Forget helium.
The real superfluid
(Sheldon:)is the fruit punch in this mug.
(Sheldon:)Reminds me of my daddy's secret
"Don't Tell Mama" juice.
(Leonard:)Uh, these are strong,
you should slow down.
(Sheldon:)Oh. I'll just take one last sip.
(Bernadette:)Ah.
(Howard:)Okay, how about this
for an invention...